我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来  我只是个普通的鉴证专员
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
But secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
但当我女儿从未来时空前来帮忙
But when my daughter came back from the future to help,
她改变了现在
she changed the present...
现在我们的世界比以往更加危险
and now our world is more dangerous than ever.
我是唯一一个来得及拯救世界的人
And I'm the only one fast enough to save it.
我是闪电侠
I am the Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
你刚从房顶上跳下来救我爸
You threw yourself off a building to save Dad?
对
Yeah.
我们都知道蝉呼吸时会发出独特声音
We all know the sound of Cicada's breathing.
他的肺部有损伤
His lungs are injured.
你不能一直这样子  这没愈合啊
We can't keep doing this. It's not healing.
迪沃占据你身体那一晚
Killer Frost has been gone
冰霜杀手就已经消失了
since the night the DeVoe took over your body.
她永远不会回来了
Is she gone for good?
我已经想尽一切办法
I've tried everything I can think of
让她重新出现
to get her to reappear.
我父亲让我来找他
My father told me to come find him.
来找我
我老爸已经死了很多年了
My dad's been dead for years.
他知道有两个你
He knew that there were two of you.
他知道冰霜杀手的真相
He knew the truth about Killer Frost.
-我们有耳目了  -我就知道你可以的
- We've got eyes and ears! - I knew you could do it.
系统访问
那个藏身之处只有一个可能
There's only one sure place somebody could hide.
唐豪瑟的一个秘密行动点
A Tannhauser black ops site.
蕾琳的香草拿铁和中杯"极速"
Vanilla latte and a Medium Zoom for Raelene.
谢谢
Thank you.
你早就该离远点
Should've left me alone.
那你就不应该存在
And you never should have existed.
闪 电 侠
第五季
第六集
我们要开工了
We are back in business.
至于工作  他的意思是
And by business, he means
比追查萨利卫星更好的工作
the better-than-Sally the satellite business.
那又是什么意思
And what does that mean?
意味着我们对于难以抓捕的蚕
That means we're getting closer to
的身份确认又更进了一步
identifying the ever-elusive Cicada.
是"蝉"  歇洛克
It's Cicada, Sherloque.
之前我黑进迪沃的卫星
Once I hacked DeVoe's satellites,
我所做的事情只是用了冲击外推算法
all I had to do was just use an impact extrapolation algorithm
去预测卫星碎片可能坠落的地点
to predict where the shrapnel would've fallen
在巴里和诺拉将强尼·凯吉
after Barry and Nora pulled a Johnny Cage
《真人快打》游戏里的人物
放上萨利卫星上之后
on Sally the satellite.
愿上帝安息她的灵魂
May God rest her soul.
所以现在我们有四十六个
So now we got 46 locations
卫星碎片可能落地的位置
where 46 pieces of shrapnel landed.
其中一个是
And once of these locations is
蝉受伤的地点
where Cicada will have been injured.
但我们现在不知道是哪个
Except we don't know which one.
也许我们知道
Or maybe we do.
在我的手被蝉的匕首划破之后
You see, after my hands got sliced by Cicada's dagger,
女神医奎恩
Dr. Quinn, Medicine Woman, here
测量过我体内的暗物质
measured the dark matter in my system.
暗物质浓度所到达的水平
And its levels of concentration were higher
是我从来没见过的
than any I'd ever seen before.
高得吓人  卫星只有一个部位
Insanely high, and the only part of the satellite
有这么高浓度的暗物质
that would have dark matter levels that high--
是核心  蝉的匕首就从这里来的
Is the core, which is where Cicada's dagger came from.
所以只要我们找到核心的位置
So we find the location of the core
我们就能知道那天晚上蝉在哪里
and we'll know where Cicada was that night.
联邦应急管理署在大悟之道之后
You know, FEMA set up sites
设置了应急站点来帮助居民
to help people after the Enlightenment.
如果蝉受伤了
If Cicada was injured,
他有可能会去其中一个站点来接受治疗
maybe he received medical treatment at one of them.
这个想法不错
That's a great idea.
我们可以联系联邦应急管理署
I mean, we could check with FEMA
来查一下在失事地点附近的站点
to see if any fathers matching Cicada's description
有没有与蝉相符受伤特征的父亲
reported any injuries near the crash site.
那我们分头行动
So, we split up.
好的  很好  我特擅长侦察追踪
Okay, great. I'm good at tracking things down.
我会尽力找到卫星核心的位置
So I will try and find the satellite core.
我跟你一起去  其他人留在这儿找名字
I will come with you and everybody else look for the names.
你介意我跟着你一起去吗
Um, do you mind if I actually come with you too?
我上星期看见你从大楼跳下去救爸爸
It's just that I saw you jump off a building last week
觉得你真的很了不起
and that was awesome.
我在想我能不能在你做侦查工作的时候
So I thought maybe I'd come with you
跟着你一起去
while you did some detective work.
我想说我们的工作
Oh, I think that two people is going to be
两个人已经够了
more than enough for what we need--
他要说的是
What he's trying to say
我们很乐意你可以和我们一起去
is that we would love to have you come with us.
好的
Okay.
好的  我去联系联邦应急管理署
All right, well, why don't I talk to FEMA
看下能不能得到些伤员名字
and see if I can get some names.
乔一直都想走出家门
Hey, I know Joe's been itching to get out of the house,
我们应该给他一个真正的徽章
and it might help to have an actual badge.
没有人破案可以像乔·韦斯特那样小菜一碟
Nobody does case snacks like Joe West.
我这就去他家拜访
I'll swing by on the way.
好的  很好
All right, cool.
斯诺巡警  现在什么情况
So, Snow Patrol, what's going on?
你来告诉我
You tell me.
我们三个人留在这里
I'm guessing it's not a coincidence
在接下来的几个小时无所事事
that we're left here with nothing to do
我猜这不是巧合
for the next few hours.
我知道我们应该等你准备好了
I know we were supposed to wait until you were ready
再去找你爸爸
to locate your dad.
可是现在我有卫星可以追踪
But I had the satellites track down
所有你爸爸可能会在的
all the decommissioned Tannhauser black ops sites
退役的唐豪瑟的秘密行动点
that your dad could possibly be in.
好吧
Okay.
然后我黑进了他们安全系统
And-- and then I hacked into their security systems.
他是最后一个登录的人
He was the last person to enter one of them.
就在他死后的一周
A week after he died.
然后他就再没离开过
And he never left.
他现在在哪
Where is he?
门开着  进来吧
It's open. Come in.
塞西尔
Hey! Cecile.
乔在吗
Is-- is Joe here?
不在  他和詹娜出去了
Uh, no. He's out with Jenna.
好吧  真扫兴
Oh, dang. Okay. Bummer.
我去买炸豆丸子  很快就回来
All right, I'll go get some falafel and come back in a bit.
等等  别走
Wait, no. Please don't--
别把我留在这  你有什么事
leave me here. Um, what did you need?
也许我可以帮你
Maybe I can help you.
我需要一个警察
Oh, I need somebody to flash a badge
而且还要气场慑人
and generally look intimidating, so.
你觉得我的气场不能慑人吗
You don't think that I can be intimidating.
天呐  你真的不觉得
Oh, my God, you don't, do you?
拉尔夫  我可是地检
Ralph, I am the district attorney.
你知道我在生女儿的同时
You know I psychically teleported the Flash
还用心理超能力把闪电侠
inside the Thinker's mind
瞬移到思考者大脑中
whilst giving birth to my daughter,
完全没打麻醉针  痛死了
sans epidural-- it hurt!
我可以说是宫缩和救世两不误
I literally saved the world between contractions,
你觉得我的气场不慑人吗
and you don't think that I am intimidating?
你的气场真是震慑到我了
I'm really intimidated right now, actually.
你的确气场慑人
You are very intimidating.
我们要做什么
Okay, what are we doing?
我们要去拿联邦应急管理署在大悟之道后
Uh, we are getting a list of FEMA recipients treated
接受治疗者的名单
after the Enlightenment
希望能从中找到禅的真实姓名
to hopefully find cicada's real name.
联邦应急管理署  我和他们合作过无数次
FEMA, come on. I worked with them a ton.
我对那个部门了如指掌
I know that org inside and out.
给我五分钟  我先去挤一下
Just, uh--oh, give me five. I gotta go pump first.
我们要挤什么
What are we pumping?
坐标 北  西
北极坐标设置好了
Coordinates are set for the North Pole.
实验室
谢谢你们跟我一起去
Thank you guys for coming with me.
你准备好就开始
Ready when you are.
好
Okay.
开始了
Here we go.
什么也看不到
Can't see anything!
我的脸彻底冻僵了
My face just went full Weeknd!
等等  我好像看到什么了
Wait, I think I see something.
这边
Over here!
什么
What?
好像是一栋建筑
I think it's a building.
有门吗
Is there a door?
我们不需要门
We don't need one.
有人吗
Hello? Anybody here?
那边
There.
你没事吧
You okay?
差不多20年前  在我父亲走进这个地方时
When my father entered this facility nearly 20 years ago,
他患有严重的渐冻症
he had severe ALS.
也许他一直待在这里是因为他走不了
Maybe the reason he never left is 'cause he couldn't.
不管在里面找到什么
Look, whatever we find in here,
我们都会陪着你的
we'll be right here with you.
我闻到了科学的气息
It smells like science in here.
你妈妈的实验室到底是做什么研究的
What kind of research does your mom's lab do, exactly?
说真的  我现在也不清楚了
I honestly don't even know anymore.
小凯
Caity?
爸  是你吗
Dad? Is that you?
我真的见到你了吗
Is this really happening?
你还活着
You're alive.
你是真的吗
Are you-- you're real?
爸  是我  我是真的
Yeah, Dad, it's me. I'm real. I'm real.
你找到我了
You found me.
你收到我的信息了
You got my message.
我在我们一起做的周期表里找到的
I did in the periodic table we made together.
用了20年才发现  但是它带我找到了你
It took me 20 years to find it, but it led me to you.
我就知道你会来的
I knew you would come.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你们
I thank all of you.
爸  这些是我的朋友  这是
Dad, these are my friends. This is--
巴里·艾伦和西斯科·拉蒙  我知道
Uh, Barry Allen and Cisco Ramon. I know.
抱歉  你们怎么会知道我们
Um, sorry. How do you know us?
我刚来这里的时候
Well, when I first came here,
我和那些科学家都保持着联络
I stayed in contact with scientists.
露易丝·林肯  维克托·弗列斯
Louise Lincoln, Victor Fries,
还有哈里森·威尔斯
and Harrison Wells.
威尔斯博士给了我尖端科研实验室监控视频的
Dr. Wells was able to give me full access to, uh,
所有访问权限
S.T.A.R. Labs video uplink.
等一下
Wait a minute.
这么久以来  你一直都能链接
You've-- you've had video link to S.T.A.R. Labs
尖端科研实验室的监控视频吗
this entire time?
当然不是  直到最近才有图像
Oh, no. God no. I mean, it hasn't worked until recently.
但是可惜  在重启之后
And unfortunately, since it rebooted,
就只能单向视频
its capabilities is only as a one-way video,
我可以看到你  但却不能和你联系
so I could see you but I couldn't reach you.
看来你在这里有很多"玩具"
Well, it looks like you had plenty of toys around here
供你消遣
to keep you company.
这个小巧的培育箱
This neat little incubator.
是用干什么的
What's it for?
我来的时候就有了
Well, that was here when I got here.
从来没用过
Never had any use for that thing.
我不明白  你为什么在这里
I don't understand. Why are you here?
你怎么还会活着呢
I mean, how are you still even alive?
渐冻症是一种可怕的疾病
ALS is a horrible disease,
我逐渐绝望
and I grew desperate,
开始用低温疗法进行实验
and I began experimenting with therapies using cryogenics.
出差错了吗
Something went wrong?
是的
Yes.
实验的危险性日益增加
The, uh, experiments became more and more dangerous.
为了所有人的安全  我把自己隔离了
and I quarantined myself for the sake of everyone's safety.
但是我成功停止了病情的恶化
I did manage to freeze the progression of that disease.
就在这个站点彻底关闭不久前
Not before the site was entirely closed out,
自那之后我就一直在这里了
and I have been here ever since.
他们在你还在这里时关闭了站点
They shut down this site while you were still in it
把你锁在了这里
and locked you in.
是我妈妈干的  对不对
It was my mother, wasn't it?
只有她有权力能命令关闭
She's the only one with an authority to shut down
唐怀瑟站点
a Tannhauser site.
听着  你母亲觉得我不和你见面
Listen, your mother thought it would be easier
会让事情更简单些
for you not to see me.
但我总是相信我能治愈这病
But I always had the faith that I could cure this thing.
所以我才给你留下线索
That's why I sent you the note.
那你  你是怎么活这么久了
So how--how did you survive here this whole time?
水  补给
Water. Rations.
时不时地在冷冻仓里呆上几个月
Spending months at a time in that cryogenic chamber.
你不需要再这么做了
Well, you don't ever have to do that again,
因为我们要把你带离这里
because we can get you out of here.
我们要找回你的生活
We're gonna give you your life back.
这里边不应该装满木架的吗
Shouldn't this place be packed to the rafters?
我是说  咱们之前不还发生过城市级灾难
I mean, we had a citywide disaster not long ago.
别担心  交给我吧
Don't worry. I got this.
是时候摆出残酷脸了
It's time to put the war face on.
伙计  拿下来
Hey, buddy, pull them out.
关掉音乐
Lose the music.
你好  我是地方检察官塞西尔·霍尔顿
Hi, I'm DA Cecile Horton.
这是我同事  拉尔夫·德比
This is my associate, Ralph Dibny.
地方检察官
DA?
有什么我能帮你的吗
How can I help you?
你是这里的现场主管吗
You the field director here?
助理  你是需要我帮你找什么吗
Assistant. You got a claim or something I can help you with?
我们想确认一起犯罪调查中的嫌疑人身份
We're trying to ID a suspect in a criminal investigation
我需要看一看你
and we're going to need to take a look at the names of
六个月来你帮助过的人的名单
all the people you've assisted in the last six months.
我不能给你任何人的名字
I can't give you anyone's names.
你得需要有搜查令才行
You'll need to get a warrant for that.
听好了  先生
Listen up, mister!
巴格·凡思
Bagger Vance!
是万斯·布兰登
It's Vance Brandon.
你给老娘听好了
You listen to me when I tell you
这里是我的地盘  孩子
that this is my town, baby.
没错  我可以让一些很坏的事情
Oh, yeah, and I can make some real
发生在你身上
bad stuff happen for you.
就是  非常  非常疯狂的事
Like, really, really no bueno.
这里是我的国家
Yeah, well, this is my country,
比你的地盘可大多了
which is a lot bigger than your town.
-这倒是真的  -所以  除非你有搜查令
- That's true. - So, until you get a warrant,
不然得不到任何东西
you're not getting anything.
但是等下  你难道  巴格  巴格你
But wait, did you--Bagger? Bagger Va--did you--
但这是我的残酷脸啊
But this my war face.
我都摆出残酷脸了
I put my war face on.
这是我的残酷脸啊  拉尔夫
That was my war face, Ralph.
没事的  我觉得你就是
It's okay, I--I think you're just--
你就是有些生疏了  仅此而已
you're--you're a little rusty, that's all.
不  刚才那生疏的
Oh, no. That was way more
可不止一点  拉尔夫
than a little rust, Ralph.
我失去了我的仙气
I've lost my mojo.
这可真是  新的旅行方式
Oh, that was a... new mode of travel.
我们将这个称为跨纬度
That is what we call an interdimensional
时空缺口
space-time breach.
需要花一点时间来熟悉
It takes a little while to get used to it.
那么  这里就是现实的尖端实验室了
So, this is S.T.A.R. Labs, IRL.
看看这景色
Look at that view.
我想做一些化验
I want to run some tests.
确保你身体一切正常
Make sure everything is all right with you.
这个城市可真漂亮
This city is so beautiful.
这里的日落
The sunsets here.
我以前经常会回想起来
I used to think about them all the time.
或许你们可以去
Hey, maybe you guys should just
散个步什么的
go for a walk or something.
试着重新熟悉下
Try and reconnect first.
好
Yeah.
不如我们出去走走
Um, why don't we go for a walk?
呼吸下新鲜空气
Get some fresh air.
我可以等下再化验
I can run my tests later.
我喜欢这计划
I love that plan.
你是怎么了
What's up with you?
兄弟  这故事里全是漏洞
Dude, this story is full of holes.
我只是想弄明白它们
I'm just trying to fill them.
诺拉的故事也充满漏洞
Nora's story had holes in them,
但她撒谎只是为了见我
and she was only lying to me 'cause she wanted to meet me.
问我享受着其中的每一秒
I've appreciated every second that we've had together so far.
凯特琳刚找回了她爸爸
Caitlin just got her dad back.
为她感到高兴吧
Let's be happy for her.
我是很高兴
Hey, I'm happy.
那我们先要做什么
So what are we doing first?
你是个极速者
Uh, well, you're a speedster.
所以我想你可以在这里转一转
So I was thinking you could run around the site.
看能不能找到核心
See if you can find the core.
我想既然是我们第一次组队
I thought, since it's our first time teaming up,
或许我能和你一起去  采访那些
maybe I could go with you and we can interview the people
大悟之道那夜在这里的人
who were here the night of the Enlightenment together.
-那还是  -不是不是
- Or no. - No, no, no.
就只是...
Yeah, it's just--
一般我都是独自采访别人
normally, I interview people by myself.
我的天  不是  没事的
Oh, oh, my God. No, no. It's fine.
我不是说想让你和我一起来回
It's--I wouldn't ask you to come speed around the city
在城里跑什么的
with me or anything like that.
-没事的  -好吧  那我就...
- It's fine. - Okay, well, I'll--
-不不  你和我一起来  -我和你一起
- No, no, no. You come with me- - I'll come with you, okay.
然后我们去采访工头
And we'll interview the foreman.
还是不要了  好吗
All right, let's not. How about that?
我们还有45个地点要搜查
Look, we have 45 more sites to search.
显然我们没有时间  并且我们要分散行动
Clearly we don't have the time and clearly we must split up.
所以你去找核心  你去和工头谈
So you go search for the core and you go talk to the foreman.
我来找线索
I will look for clues.
这就是调查如何失败的
And this is how investigations collapse.
宝贝你好
Hey, babe.
没有  母女组合的开局可能不太顺利
No, the mother-daughter team-up is kinda off to a rocky start.
不好说  我想我们会成功的
But I don't know, I think we'll get there.
怎么说
So?
核不在这
The core's not here.
要不你去其他地点搜查
Why don't you go search the other sites?
我们继续搜查这里
We'll finish up here.
不过你不想那么做  对吗
Well, no, you don't want to do that, do you, no?
因为你不是来调查的
Because, um, you're not here to investigate, are you?
你来是为了和你母亲共处的  对吗
No, you're here to spend time with your mother, right?
我只是想如果我们调查同一件案子
Well, I just thought maybe we would find something
会找到我们的共通之处
in common if we worked on a case together.
她很擅长从别人那里打探消息
But she's really good at prying information out of people.
没错
Believe me, and...
而我行动很快
I'm fast on my feet.
我还是回尖端科研实验室吧
I'm gonna go back to S.T.A.R. Labs.
等等
Hold on, wait.
我有另一个计划去找这个核
I have another plan to try and find this core.
需要你和你的母亲一起
It involves you and your mother.
樱桃汽水  爆米花
So, uh, cherry soda. Popcorn.
我还很久没喝吉斯特的咖啡了
I haven't had a cup of Jitters coffee in quite a while.
不过我最想念的是
But the thing that I miss the most was--
花生果酱华夫饼
Peanut butter and jelly waffles.
你以前做华夫饼的时候妈妈很不喜欢
Yeah, Mom used to hate it when you made those.
你妈妈总是希望生活里
Yeah, well, your mom always wanted
有更美好的事物
the nicer things in life, I guess,
而我简简单单就很开心
and I was happy with simple.
你俩能走到一起是个奇迹
It's a wonder you two ever got together.
-她怎么样了  -老样子
- How is she? - The same.
我不常见她
I don't really see her that often,
而我和她联系的时候  她总是很冷淡
and when I do, she's cold as ice.
而现在  得知她对你做了那些事情
And now, after what she did to you--
小凯  她可能有些冷淡
Oh, well, look, she may be a little bit chilly,
但她是爱你的
but she does love you, Caity.
你不在  生活很艰难
It's been really hard without you.
只有我和她  真的很难
I mean, just me and her. It was tough.
-是的  -我经历了很多事情
- Yeah. - I've been through a lot.
大都是因我而起
A lot of that has to do with me.
不  不是的
No.
你听我说  我一直没有陪伴你
No, no, listen, and--and I wasn't there for you.
这么多年过去了
All these years-- they went by and I--
小凯  我想补偿你
I want to make it up to you, Caity.
我确实应该陪伴在你身边
I mean, I really should've been there for you, right?
我希望我能
I mean--and I wish that I could just--
爸爸  天哪
Dad? Oh, my God.
爸爸  来坐下
Dad. Here, sit.
天哪  爸爸
Oh, my God. Dad?
爸爸  爸爸
Dad, Dad.
小凯
Caity?
爸爸  我在这
Dad? I'm right here.
你看到我的病了
You saw my disease?
真皮层在结晶
Yeah, uh... the dermis is crystallizing.
并且还在扩散
And it's spreading.
你昏迷的时候我做了一些测试
I ran some tests while you were unconscious.
你有低温恶性肿瘤
You have a cryogenic malignancy
以及躯体变异
and a somatic mutation.
这不会传染但是
It's not contagious but--
它在改写我的基因序列
It's rewriting my genetic code.
如果继续恶化下去  你会
And if it continues, you could--
死去
Die.
我治好了我的渐冻症
Well, I cured my ALS,
但却引起了更致命的疾病
but I created something even more deadly.
每次我情绪激动的时候  肿瘤都会扩散
Every time my emotions spike, my malignancy spreads.
例如你气愤或者害怕的时候吗
Like when you're angry or scared?
我宁愿当初没有那么做
I wish I had just left well enough alone.
对你我都好
For both of us.
等等  我也有渐冻症的遗传标记吗
Wait, did I have the genetic marker for ALS too
你在尝试治好我吗
and you tried to cure me?
我的能力是因你而来的
So my powers came from you?
冰霜杀手是对我的治疗
Killer Frost is my cure?
冰霜杀手
Killer Frost?
你可能听过另一个名字
You may know her by a different name.
喀俄涅
Khione.
爸爸  你对我做了什么
Dad, what did you do to me?
我不想让渐冻症在你身上显现
I wasn't gonna let the ALS manifest in you
就像我这样
like it did in me.
所以你在你自己女儿身上用了
So you used experimental cryogenic gene therapy
实验性低温基因疗法
on your own daughter?
我已经在自己身上试过了
I had already done it on myself.
小凯  我针对疗法做了改动
Caity, I made alterations to the treatment.
我尝试让它更安全
I tried to make it safer, Caity,
在我开始对你治疗后不久
and you started to exhibit dual personality
你就开始出现双重人格
soon after I treated you.
这个喀俄涅或者冰霜杀手人格
So is, um, Khione or Killer Frost--
她还存在吗
is she still around?
不  她已经消失了一段时间了
No, she--she's been gone for a little while,
但她仍是我的一部分
but she's still a part of me.
那你的双重人格是什么
So where's your dual personality?
你和凯特琳携带同样的遗传标记
You and Caitlin carry the same markers,
你们采用了同样的疗法
you took the same cure.
你的第二重身份呢
Where your Khione?
我从来没有过
I never had one.
这也许就是为什么
That's probably why...
我快要死了  而你没有
I'm dying and you're not.
如果使用我的细胞来制造血清
Okay, what if we use my cells to create a serum
去稳定你的身体呢
to stabilize your body?
我们得让你的原子停止振动
Um, we have to stop your atoms from oscillating.
来让你的体温达到绝对零度
So get your body to a temperature of absolute zero.
凯特琳  那样会杀死他
Caitlin, that could kill him.
理论上  因为低温基因疗法的缘故
My cells can theoretically
我的细胞可以在理论上
withstand subzero temperatures
可以承受零下的低温
because of my cryogenic gene therapy.
但问题是要接近于绝对零度
But the problem is getting to absolute zero.
我们可以使用激光降温序列
We could use a laser cooling array.
国防部最近在城外的基地建了一个
The DOD just constructed one at their site outside of town.
-我可以去看看  -好的太棒了
- I could check it out. - Okay, great.
我去开始制作血清
I'll get started on the serum.
不  不  等等  等一下
No, no, wait. Hold on.
我们不能就这么黑进美国国防部
We--we can't just hack into
那价值50亿的安全系统
the DOD's $5 billion security system.
西斯科
Cisco.
我才刚找回我爸  我不能失去他
I just got my dad back. I can't let him die.
我看看我能帮忙什么
I'll see what I can do.
这是这周第五个被切伤的人
It's the fifth person to be sliced up this week.
带他去3号手术室
Take him to OR Three.
天啊  你怎么了
Oh, my God. What happened to you?
-我很好  -那需要缝合
- I'm fine. - I need to stitch that up.
你身上有擦伤  可能还有内伤
You've got abrasions, possible internal injuries.
如果你继续到外面
You keep going out there,
你的下场就是被装在装尸袋里
you're gonna be back here in a body bag.
你不能被卷入其中
You can't be a part of this.
你知道在过去4年里我
Do you know how many patients I've seen
见到了多少因为超能力者
come in this hospital the past four years
而进医院的伤患吗
because of those metas out there?
我刚治疗了一个被剃刀人袭击的
I just treated a man who was attacked by
男患者  而你居然要告诉我
a human razor blade, and you wanna say
我不能被卷入其中
I'm not a part of this?
我解决那个剃刀超能力者了
Oh, I got that razor meta.
同样地  我也会解决其他的超能力者
Just like I'll get the rest of them.
我知道你这么做的原因
I know why you're doing this.
我知道那个陷入昏迷状态的小女孩
And I know that little girl laying in a coma
不是我的家人  但你不是唯一每天
is not my family, but you are not the only one
因为她没有苏醒而感到难过的人
whose heart breaks every day she doesn't wake up.
格雷丝才是需要被帮助的人  而不是我
Grace is the one that needs help. Not me.
你现在要让开道  医生
Now, are you gonna get out of my way, Doc?
还是要呼叫警卫
Or are you gonna call security?
刚刚到底发生了什么
What the heck happened back there?
我僵住了
I froze up.
听着
Look.
当我还在中城警局的时候
When I got canned from CCPD,
我遇见了一些游走在灰色地带的人
I fell in with some legally questionable individuals.
他们是一些非常非常恐怖的人
These are some scary, scary people,
但他们有个共同点
but they all had one thing in common.
他们都很害怕塞西尔·决定你命运·霍尔顿
They were all terrified of Ce-Seal-Your-Fate Horton .
而我一点也不相信
And I don't believe for one second that
那个女人已经不见了
that woman has gone anywhere.
永远也别那样称呼我
Don't ever call me that again.
我很抱歉  天啊  我以为  以为我们
I'm sorry. Geez. I thought I--I thought we were bonding
有了什么连结  但我想我错了
and having a moment, but I think I crossed the line.
我不是有意要
I didn't really mean to--
开玩笑啦  这是个玩笑  我在开玩笑
I'm kidding. It's a joke. I was joking.
天啊  我真的骗到你了
My gosh, I really got you.
你不用那么紧张
You didn't have to get so nervous about it.
紧张  就像联邦应急管理署的人一样
Nervous. Like the FEMA guy did.
拉尔夫  我不认为我那时候僵住了
Ralph, I don't think I froze up back there.
对对对  你  你现在是共情者了
Right. Right, you're-- you're an Empath now.
你的能力让你感受到他的恐惧
Your powers let you experience his fear.
你是闪电侠小队的迪安娜·特洛伊
You're--you're the Deanna Troi of Team Flash.
《星际迷航:下一代》中拥有感知情感的超能力的虚拟人物
我不知道那是谁  但如果他在我们
I have no idea who that is, but if he got that scared
问他受害者名单时感到害怕
when we asked him about the victims list--
就说明他在隐瞒着什么
It's because he's hiding something.
对
Yes.
你这  你这鼻子是怎么了
What's, uh, what's happening with your nose right now?
这是当我察觉到秘密时的小动作
Oh, when I smell a mystery, that's my thing. I do that.
-真恶心  -会吗  你不...
- That's nasty. - It is? You don't--
-拜托停下来  -你不喜欢吗
- Please stop. - You don't like it?
划船引领我们  领着我们
C'est l'aviron qui nous mène, qui nous mène
划船让我们兴奋
C'est l'aviron qui nous mène en haut
划船引领我们  领着我们
C'est l'aviron qui nous mène, qui nous mène
划船让我们兴奋
C'est l'aviron qui nous mène en haut
他唱那首歌已经两个小时了
He has been singing that same song for the last two hours.
我知道  我知道
I know, I know.
现在来泡茶  你是认真的吗
Are you seriously making tea right now?
茶  是的  是的  甘菊茶
Le thé. Oui. Right, chamomile.
你知道的  以刺激大脑  诚实地说
You know, to stimulate the brain, but also, frankly,
还有  消化系统
the digestive system.
因为从我到这里开始
Right, because since I've arrived at here,
我一直像塞车一样便秘
I've been backed up like a traffic jam.
那真恶心  恶心至极
That is so disgusting. Beyond disgusting.
我们在你泡茶时
How are we supposed to investigate
要怎么调查  歇洛克
when you're making tea, Sherloque?
小姐  你看起来很烦恼
Well, you seem very annoyed, mademoiselle.
-不要废话  夏洛克  -是歇洛克
- No shrap, Sherlock. - Sherloque.
抱歉说话冲了  妈妈
Sorry for the language, Mom.
没关系
It's okay.
看
Hey, look.
卫星坠落之夜有一个嘉年华会
There was a carnival the night the satellite crashed.
如果我爸爸所说蝉是个父亲是对的  那么...
If my dad is right about Cicada being a father, then maybe--
他可能带他的孩子来这里了
He might've brought his kid here.
没错
Exactly.
但  我是说  我搜遍这里了
But, I mean, I ran all over this place.
没有看见核心
There's no core in sight.
划船引领我们  领着我们
C'est l'aviron qui nous mène, qui nous mène
如果
What if...
核心掉到水里了
The core fell into the water.
那你要如何取回它
How you will retrieve it?
诺拉  你何不造一个漩涡
Nora, why don't you create a vortex like your dad did
就像你爸在对付鲨鱼王时做的
when he fought King Shark?
不然  我们学你对付哈特尼斯的方法
Oh, no, or what if we do what you did with the Hotness?
你知道那件事
You know about that?
当然  我让乔爷爷告诉我所有
Yeah, of course. I made Papa Joe tell me everything about
我妈还是极速者时的事情
when my mom was a speedster.
所以我们要怎么做
So how do we do it?
你就  你要以紧密的路线
Well, you just, um--you run back and forth in a--
来回地跑
in a really tight formation.
然后你要用脚跟把水吸上来
And you want to pull the water up with your heels.
好的  这会让水离开岸边
Okay, right, which will drive the water away from the shore.
没错
Exactly.
-酷炫  -没错
-Schway. -Yeah.
你认为我可以做到吗
Do you think I can do it?
对  诺拉  你做得到
Yeah, Nora, you got this.
好
Okay.
四个卫星
Four satellites?
交给西斯科  他能搞定
Give them to Cisco. He's got 'em.
国防部网站  没问题  一天就完事
DOD sites? There you go. All in a day's work for him.
你们觉得我什么都能黑进去是吧
You all think I can just hack anything, huh?
没错
Yeah.
我就是什么都能黑进去
I can hack anything.
在这呢
There you are.
我找到进国防部基地的路了
Found a path into the DOD base.
只要西斯科能关掉内部的警报就行
As long as Cisco can shut down the interior alarms, it'll work.
很好  我平衡好这份血清
Awesome. I just need to balance this serum
我们就可以行动了
and we should be good to go.
谢谢你  小凯
Thank you for this, Caity.
你为我做的远远超过了你的职责
I mean, what you're doing is beyond the call.
当然了  你是我爸爸
Of course, you're my dad.
我愿意为你做任何事情
I'd do anything for you.
他不是你爸爸
He's not your dad.
眼熟吗
Look familiar?
西斯科  你在说什么
Cisco. What are you talking about?
他是我爸爸
This is my father.
我回到唐豪瑟的秘密行动点
I went back to the Tannhauser black ops site,
接收到一个震波
and I picked up a vibe.
我看见他在实验室工作
I saw him working in the lab--
西斯科  你的震波最近有点容易差错
Cisco, your vibes have been a little problematic--
我亲眼所见不会错  我看见他站在培养皿旁边
I know what I saw. I saw him standing over the incubator,
他说那培养皿没有用
the one he claimed he had no use for,
但他却在使用它
and he was working on this.
皮移植片  跟这一切有什么关系吗
Skin grafts? What does this have to do with anything?
这听上去可能很不可思议
This is gonna sound whacked-out,
但万一你爸爸在想办法治疗渐冻症的时候
but what if, when you dad tried to cure his ALS,
不仅仅只是把皮肤结晶化了呢
it didn't just give him crystallized skin?
万一他真的创造出了一个双重人格呢
What if it really did create that dual personality?
-这个冰霜杀手  -你是这么想的
-This Killer Frost? - That's who you think this is?
这是另一个托马斯  他戴着用这些皮移植片
Thomas' alter ego wearing a copy of his face
复制成的托马斯的脸
made out of these skin grafts?
我知道这听上去...
Yes, I know. I know it-it sounds--
听上去很荒谬
It sounds absurd,
但我能理解为什么拉蒙先生会有这种假设
but I can see where Mr. Ramon is getting his hypothesis.
我的低温恶性肿瘤蔓延得比我所说的更严重
My, uh, cryo-malignancy spread further than I admitted,
它已经蔓延到了我的脸  手  手臂和胸
and it's afflicted my face, my hands, my arms, my chest.
我用实验室找到的干细胞做这些皮移植片
And I created those skin grafts from stem cells
是为了掩盖之后病情的恶化
that I found in the lab in order to cover any further outbreaks.
你在说谎
You're lying to us.
-西斯科  -凯特琳  你要看清楚
- Cisco-- - Caitlyn, you have to see--
不  你不要再扰乱我们了
No, you need to leave us alone.
-拜托  -马上离开
- Please-- - Now!
我去吧
I got it.
兄弟  我们得聊聊
Dude. Hey dude, we need to talk.
为什么  我觉得刚刚那场激烈对峙已经足够了
Why? I thought that dramatic confrontation worked perfectly.
-我们都想帮凯特琳  -是吗
- We all want to help Caitlin. - Oh, do you?
我想让凯特琳有机会和爸爸在一起
Yeah, I want Caitlin to have a chance to be with her father.
就像诺拉有机会跟你在一起一样
Just like Nora got the chance to be with you?
你看  你的问题就在这里
See, this is your problem.
你觉得这只是个
You think that this is just another perfect
完美的父女相认和团圆
father-daughter pairing, reunited.
我没有被我的感情蒙蔽
I'm not blinded by my feelings.
你的感情也没帮你看清形势
Well, they're not helping you see any clearer.
你不要再站在诺拉爸爸的角度想这个问题了
You gotta stop thinking about this like Nora's dad
而应该站在鉴证员的角度
and start thinking about it like a CSI.
好吗
Please?
这么做不是为了我  是为了她
Don't do it for me. Do it for her.
我不是叫你们滚了吗
Didn't I tell you to get lost?
没错  我们还要谢谢你呢
Yes, you did. Thanks for that.
正好给我们时间查你的底细
Gave us time to pull your file.
你没有什么前科
You don't have any priors,
但我倒找到一堆没交的停车罚单
but I did find about a dozen outstanding parking tickets, though.
天哪
Oh, no.
是什么车的罚单来着  是...
For, uh, what was it? It was, um--
哦对  是一辆兰博基尼
Oh, yeah, a Lamborghini.
真拉风
Hmm. Vroom, vroom.
一个公务员怎么买得起二十万的车
How does a civil servant afford a $200,000 car?
我要叫保安了
Okay, I'm calling security.
请便
Please do.
我正想举报一起保险诈骗案呢
I can't wait to report a case of insurance fraud.
你告诉人们  他们的索赔被拒绝了
You've been telling citizens their claims have been denied
却偷偷把政府给的钱
and then pocketing the cash for yourself
放到自己口袋里
when the government pays up.
正因为这样  联邦应急管理署的金库才会
That's why this FEMA center's emptier than Grandma's whiskey
比我们德比家圣诞晚宴上奶奶的威士忌酒瓶还空
at a Dibny Christmas dinner.
你们拿不出证据证明
You can't prove any of this.
有本事你试试
Try me.
每个人的资料都在这里了
That's everyone.
姓名  住址  事故那晚的地点
Names, addresses, location the night of the crash.
所以...  我那事能不说出去吗
So... this is gonna stay between us?
你一直从无辜受害者那里获利
You've been profiting off of innocent victims.
二十分钟前  我给你在华府的上级打了个电话
You know I put a call into your superiors in D.C. 20 minutes ago.
我重回最佳状态了  凡西
I got my groove back, Vancey.
所以我知道害怕的人是你  而不是我
That's how I know it's you that's scared and not me.
我们都认识并喜爱的那个
Now there's the old Ce-Seal-Your-Fate Horton
塞西尔·决定你命运·霍尔顿回来了
we all know and love.
如果你是来帮西斯科说话的  还是算了吧
If you came to defend Cisco, please don't bother.
他只是关心你
He just cares about you.
拜托  如果那不是我爸爸
Come on, don't you think I wouldn't know
难道我会不知道吗
if that wasn't actually my father?
怎么  连你也这样吗
You too? Really?
听着  我想相信他是你爸爸
Listen, I wanted to believe that that's your dad
他是好人  因为我想让你高兴
and that he's a good guy because I want you to be happy.
但我...  我不知道
But I don't--I don't know.
可能我看得不够明白
Maybe I haven't been seeing clearly.
这人的故事有很多自相矛盾的地方
There is a lot about this guy's story that doesn't add up.
这人  这人是我爸爸
This guy? This guy is my father.
是他在我长水痘的时候抱着我
He's the man who held me when I had chickenpox.
是他告诉我并让我坚信
Who told me I could be anything I wanted to
我可以成为我想要成为的一切
and made me believe it.
所以拜托你们不要把他当犯人对待
So please stop treating him like he's a criminal.
好的
Okay.
你知道我和我妈妈有多疏远
You know how estranged I am from my mother
冰霜杀手没了我感觉多空虚
and how empty I felt without Killer Frost.
他是我唯一的家人了
He is the only family that I have left.
凯特琳  不是这样的  我们也是你的家人
But Caitlin, that's not true. We're your family too.
我们只是让你敞开心胸
And we're only asking you to keep an open mind
因为我们在乎你
because we care about you.
尤其是西斯科
Especially Cisco.
如果能让你感觉好一点的话
If it'll make you feel better,
你可以问他问题
you can ask him your questions,
但只能在我给他注射血清以后
but only after I give him the serum.
-怎么了  -我的天
- What's wrong? - Oh, my God.
什么
What?
如果我给人类注射血清
If I give this serum to a human,
这会抑制他们恶性的一面
it will suppress their malignant side.
但是如果我给低温的超能力者注射
But if I give it to a cryogenic meta-human,
这可能会永久抑制他们人性的一面
it will permanently suppress their human side.
如果那是你爸爸的第二自我
If that's your father's alter ego--
那他正试着除掉我爸爸
He's trying to wipe out my dad.
他需要你的细胞来制作血清
He needed your cells to make the serum.
凯特琳  来找我
"Caitlin, come find me."
小凯
Caity.
发生什么了
What's going on?
爸爸  为什么
Dad, why?
既然你们都在这里...
Well... I guess, as you're all here...
你有这么聪明的朋友  凯特琳
You have such smart friends, Caity.
你们肺里的冷冻液
That frozen liquid in your lungs
将会变成微小的冰柱
is gonna be turning into tiny icicles.
让你们很难呼吸
Making it very difficult for you to breathe.
但是别担心
But no worries.
你们很快就会昏过去
You'll pass out soon.
凯特琳  凯特琳  醒醒
Caitlin. Hey! Caitlin, wake up.
-你还好吗  -嗯  我还好
- Hey, are you okay? - Yeah, yeah, I'm okay.
我爸爸走了吗
Um, is my dad gone?
他拿走了血清
He took the serum.
都是我的错
This is all my fault.
爸爸回来我太激动了
I was so excited to have my dad back
我没能看清他到底是谁
that I--I couldn't see who he really was.
我欠你们俩一个道歉
I owe you both an apology.
没事的
Hey, it's okay.
我们会抓到他的
We'll get him.
各位  来这里
Hey, guys, get in here.
来吧
Come on.
请看
Eyes, please.
-什么  -他在美国国防部里  看吧
- What? - He's at the DOD site. Look.
那栋楼只有零下七度吗
That building's 7 below?
看着温度  它下降了
Look at the temperature. Look at it drop.
他启动了负向阵列
He initiated the negative array
但没有密封
but didn't seal it.
房间是零下七度  但阵列是零下一百度
The room is -7, but the array is -100.
那东西太冷了
That thing's so freaking cold,
把整栋楼都冻住了
it's freezing the whole building.
等等  按这个速度  五分钟以内
Wait, at this rate, in 5 minutes,
温度就会变成零下460度
the temperature will be -460 degrees,
或者说  绝对零度
AKA absolute zero.
那个时候  他可以向自己注射我的血清
At which point, he can inject himself with my serum.
然后让自己完全变成冰柱
And turn himself into a full-on icicle.
冰柱  不是时候啊
Icicle, that's-- not the time.
-我们该走了  -我们行动吧
- We gotta go. - Let's do it.
你的手怎么办
Hey, what-- what about your hands?
你是我的朋友  我的家人  我要去了
You're my friend, my family. I'm going.
快好了
Almost there.
闪电侠
Flash.
你们还没意识到速度和寒冷不相容吗
Don't you realize that speed and cold don't mix?
这个机器产生的同位素
This machine is capable of producing isotopes
能用来冻结二氧化碳
that can freeze carbon dioxide.
你们跑不到这里来
You can't run in here.
更多的超级英雄要被冻结了
More superheroes to freeze.
阵列里零下220度了  你们还有一分钟
The array's at -220. You have one minute.
你们不如我想象的聪明
You people are not as smart as I thought.
各位  怎么了
Guys, what's happening?
这个房间里的温度在下降
The temperature in the room is dropping.
大家都很冷  他们的原子接近静止了
Everyone's so cold, their atoms are hitting near stasis.
为什么我看不到自己的呼吸
Why--why can't I see my breath?
太冷了  空气里没有水分了
It's too cold. There's no moisture in the air.
西斯科  你还好吗
Cisco, are you okay?
不  至少我什么都感觉不到了
No. At least I can't feel anything.
各位  阵列里零下350度了
Guys, the array's at -350 degrees.
他马上就要进入完全的冰柱状态了
He's gonna be able to go full icicle soon.
快啊
Come on.
-四十五秒  -我们该做什么
- Forty-five seconds. - What do we do?
闪电
Lightning.
用你的闪电来抵抗寒冷
Use your lightning to counter the cold
也许你可以用足够的加温来制止他
and maybe you can warm up enough to stop him.
我们一直都在试着这么做
We've been trying to do it this whole time.
太冷了
It's too cold.
说真的  我冻僵了
I'm literally fr--freezing.
零下399度  你们还有三十秒
-399, you have 30 seconds.
你们的体温下降得太快了
Your temperature is dropping too quickly.
你们很快就会陷入低温休克的
You're gonna go into hypothermic shock soon.
但凯特琳不会
But not Caitlin.
看  凯特琳的体温是正常的
Look, Caitlin's body temperature is normal.
凯特琳  你一定是免疫了
Caitlin, you must be immune.
但是冰霜杀手已经消失了
But Killer Frost is gone.
很显然  她还在
Well, clearly, she's not.
各位  零下400度  我们还有二十秒
Guys, 400 degrees. We got 20 seconds.
凯特琳  你可以做到
Caitlin, you can do it.
集中精神就好
Just concentrate.
爸爸
Dad!
拜托  我知道你在里面
Please, I know you're in there.
别这么做
Don't do this.
你觉得托马斯能听到你吗  凯特琳
Do you think Thomas can hear you, Caity?
托马斯什么都听不见
Thomas hasn't been able to hear anything
已经很久了
for a very long time.
-那是什么  -零下460度  我们太晚了
- What is that? - 460 degrees. We're too late.
他击败了我们
He beat us.
不
No!
我的女儿  你回来了
My daughter. You've returned!
你不是我的家人
You're not my family.
他们才是
They are.
你在乎我只不过是因为你想要血清
You only gave a damn about me because you wanted that serum.
但我可以和你分享
But I--I can share it with you.
想想看
Just imagine.
咱们俩可以做我们自己  什么都不用怕
The two of us, free to be ourselves without fear.
你很强大
You are strong.
我们一起可以更加强大
We can be even stronger together.
我很强大因为我生命中
I'm strong because I have people in my life
有真正在乎我的人
who actually care about me.
真的吗
Do you?
不
No!
小凯
Caity?
-爸爸  -你找到我了
- Dad? - You found me?
温度在上升
Temperature's rising.
怎么了  大家都还好吗
What's happening? Is everyone okay?
-我觉得是  -需要点帮助
- I think so. - A little help?
去帮西斯科
Get Cisco.
很好
Oh, yeah. That's good.
是的
Yeah.
好
Okay.
我爸
My dad.
我们的爸爸
Our dad.
他刚在这  但我又失去他了
He was here, but... I lost him.
我们会把他找回来的  我们一起
We'll get him back. Together.
你不再是一个人了
You're not alone anymore.
我也不是了
Neither am I.
这一区域没有寒冷信号
No cold signature in the area.
雪国老人一定在很远的地方
Snow Country for Old Men must be miles away,
反正他一定不在中城
'cause he sure as hell isn't in Central City.
我们必须得找到他
Well, we have to find him.
如果我爸一点都不剩的话
I mean, Icicle wouldn't have gone through all this trouble
冰柱不会这么大费周章地去杀他
to kill my Dad if there wasn't a piece of him still left.
我们会找到他的
We'll find him.
我用震波发现的东西都不是你爸爸的记忆
All the things I vibed, they weren't memories of your dad.
是他第二自我的
They were of his alter ego.
我爸想尽力保护我
My dad was trying to protect me.
你知道吗  我妈可能也是
You know what? My mom probably was too.
我是说  她只是想保护我的安全
I mean, she was just trying to keep me safe.
一直以来我都以为她是坏人
All this time, I thought she was the villain.
我为什么看不出是他
How could I not see it was him?
别怪自己
Hey, don't beat yourself up.
斯旺  佐勒蒙
Thawne. Zolomon.
我们看到人的善良之处  这就是我们
We see the good in people. That's just who we are.
我希望这点永不改变
I hope that never changes.
这有些其他东西  你们应该看下
There's something else you guys should see.
一直以来  我们一直想知道
All this time, we've been trying to figure out
冰霜杀手怎么消失的
how Killer Frost disappeared,
但一直以来看待的方式都是错的
but we've been looking at it all wrong.
我们一直认为迪沃用融点的超能力
We've been thinking DeVoe used Melting Point's powers,
改变了你的超能力者基因
that he changed your meta DNA
从你体中消除了冰霜杀手
and removed Killer Frost from you.
但今晚  你证明了她仍是你的一部分
But tonight, you proved that she's still a part of you.
那什么导致她的消失
So what caused her to leave?
迪沃用一组不同的超能力
DeVoe used a different set of powers.
-头脑风暴  -头脑风暴
- Brainstorm. - Brainstorm.
他们做的是制造了一个心理阻隔
All they did was create a mental block.
你今晚打破了它  所以她再次出现
One you broke through tonight, so you can do that again.
你得学会如何打破
You just gotta learn how.
我认为是时候再次介绍一位老朋友了
I think it's time we reintroduce an old friend.
哈里的内心活动缓冲器
Harry's mental activity dampener.
它帮助我听到了她
It'll help me hear her.
没错
That's right.
我希望你用它越多
It's my hope that the more you use it,
越能和她联系起来
the more you connect with her.
最终你就不再需要它了
Eventually, you won't need it anymore.
谢谢
Thank you.
各位  来极速实验室一下
Guys, we need you in the Speed Lab.
好的  就交给你了
All right. We'll leave you to it.
你好  陌生人
Hey, stranger.
你好
Hey.
我们可有得谈了
Well, we sure have a lot to talk about.
萨利的心
Oh! Sally's heart!
你把它带回来了
You brought it back.
的确  多亏了他俩
We did, thanks to these two
还有他们的演绎能力
and their deductive abilities.
还有我们的海啸冲击技能  对吧
And our tidal-wave-breaking skills. Right?
有其母必有其女
Like mother, like daughter.
这个在这安全吗
Uh, is it safe for this to be here?
安全  一点暗物质不会伤害任何人
Yeah, a little dark matter never hurt anybody.
什么
What?
我们之前见过这个形状
We've seen this puzzle piece before.
我们卫星给予的  现在我们要收回了
Our satellite giveth, and now we must taketh away.
我觉得我们终于可以开始行动了
I think we can finally do that.
我们从联邦应急管理署得到了一份
We got a list from FEMA of everyone who reported injuries
大悟之道那晚上报受伤的名单
the night of the Enlightenment.
没有一个符合蝉的描述
None of them matched Cicada's description.
但有三个孩子
But there were three kids
他们被卫星碎片击中
who were hit by pieces of shrapnel from the satellite.
其中两个是双胞胎  他们的爸爸去世了
Two of them are twins whose father is deceased.
还有一个是个十岁的女孩
Third is a ten-year-old girl,
叫格蕾丝·吉本斯
by the name of Grace Gibbons.
如果如我爸所料蝉是个父亲的话  那么
So if my dad's right and Cicada's a father, then...
我们可能找到了他女儿
We may have just found his daughter.
奥林
Orlin?
Orlin.
我弄好这边之后就弄你的胸
After I fix up your side, I'm gonna patch up your chest.
不
No.
这让我更强壮了
It's making me stronger.